Guide to the Montana postcard collection 1893-2008, bulk 1905-1950
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Subject, 1893-1996; Series III
  - Victor (Mont.) (Box 19)
  - Virginia City (Mont.) (Box 19)
    - Buildings
  - Virginia City (Mont.) (Box 20)
    - Logging and mining
    - Road Agents
    - Streets
    - Views
  - Warland (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Warm Springs Creek (Box 20)
  - West Yellowstone (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Wheeler (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Whitcomb (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - White Sulphur Springs (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Whitefish Lake (Box 20)
  - Whitefish (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Whitehall (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Willow Creek (Box 20)
  - Windham (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Wise River (Box 20)
  - Wolf Creek Canyon (formerly Prickly Pear Canyon) (Box 20)
  - Wolf Point (Mont.) (Box 20)
  - Yellowstone National Park (Box 20)
    Many of the Yellowstone National Park postcards are numbered sets associated with a publishing company, so these postcards are arranged alphabetically by the name of the publisher. Publishers whose names begin with the letters A to Sa are in box 15. Box 16 contains letters Sc to Z. The subjects listed below are represented in these sets. Contact the Photograph Archives for an index of subjects by publisher.
    - Angel Terrace
    - Bears
    - Big Blue Spring
    - Biscuit Basin
    - Bison
    - Buffalo Bill Dam and Reservoir (formerly Shoshone Dam)
    - Camping
    - Canyon Hotel
    - Castle Geyser
    - Cathedral Rocks
    - Chittenden Bridge
    - Cleopatra Terrace
    - Crossed Sabres Ranch (formerly Holm Lodge)
    - Crystal Falls
    - Deer
    - Devil's Inkstand
    - Eagle Nest Rock
    - Emerald Pool
    - Excelsior Geyser
    - Firehole Falls
    - Firehole River
    - Fishing
    - Fishing Cone
    - Fort Yellowstone
    - Fountain Geyser
    - Fountain Paint Pot
    - Gardiner (Mont.)
    - Gardner Canyon
    - Gardner River
    - Giant Geyser
    - Gibbon Canyon
    - Gibbon Falls
    - Golden Gate Canyon
    - Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone River
    - Grand Loop Road
    - Grotto Geyser
    - Hoodoos
    - Jupiter Terrace
    - Kepler Cascades
    - Lake Hotel
    - Liberty Gap
    - Lone Star Geyser
    - Lower Falls of the Yellowstone
    - Mammoth Hot Springs
    - Mammoth Hot Springs Hotel
    - Minerva Terrace
    - Minute Geyser
    - Morning Glory Pool
    - Mount Haynes (formerly Mount Burley)
    - Mud Geyser
    - Mud Volcano
    - Natural Bridge
    - Norris Geyser Basin
    - Oblong Geyser
    - Obsidian Cliff
    - Old Faithful Geyser
    - Opal Terrace
    - Orange Spring Mound
    - Oregon Short Line Depot
    - Petrified trees
    - Pulpit Terrace
    - Punch Bowl Spring
    - Rainbow Pool
    - Rangers
    - Red Rock
    - Riverside Geyser
    - Roosevelt Arch
    - Sapphire Pool
    - Sheepeater Cliffs
    - Shoshone Canyon
    - Shoshone Lake
    - Silver Gate
    - Spiral Bridge
    - Sponge Geyser
    - Stagecoaches
    - Steamboats
    - Sunset Lake
    - Teakettle Spring
    - Tower Fall
    - Trout Creek
    - U.S. Highway 212
    - Undine Falls
    - Upper Falls of the Yellowstone
    - Upper Geyser Basin
    - Viewbooks
    - Virginia Cascade
    - West Yellowstone (Mont.)
    - Wylie Hotel
    - Wylie Permanent Camp
    - Yellowstone Lake
    - Yellowstone River
  - Yellowstone River (Box 20)
  - Yellowtail Dam (Box 20)
  - Zortman (Mont.) (Box 20)
- Oversized Postcards, 1907-1996; Series IV
  - Artwork (Box 21)
    - Harrison, Robert -- Sculptures
    - Haynes, F. Jay (Frank Jay), 1853-1921 -- Photographs
      Reproductions of F. Jay Haynes photographs not published by Haynes.
    - Mihalic, David. -- Paintings
    - Paxson, E. S., 1852-1919. -- Paintings
    - Peters, Les -- Paintings
    - Ralston, J. K., 1896- -- Paintings
    - Reedstrom, Ernest Lisle -- Paintings
    - Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909 -- Paintings
    - Russell, Charles M. (Charles Marion), 1864-1926 -- Paintings
    - Van Tassell, C. (Charles), b. 1858 -- Drawings
  - Bighorn Canyon National Recreation Area (Mont. and Wyo.) (Box 21)
  - Billings (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Bison, American (Box 21)
    - Big Medicine
  - Chinook (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Deer (Box 21)
  - Dillon, (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Essex (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Flathead Lake (Mont.) and Kerr Dam (Box 21)
  - Fort Peck Lake (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Galata (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Glacier National Park (Mont.) (Box 21)
    - Lake McDonald
    - Logan Pass
    - Many Glacier Hotel
    - McDonald Creek
    - Mount Gould
    - Mount Wilbur
    - St. Mary Lake
    - Trick Falls
    - Two Medicine Lake
  - Great Falls (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Haugan (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Helena (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Highways and interstates (Box 21)
  - Indians (Box 21)
  - Little Bighorn Battlefield National Monument (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Mission Range (Box 21)
  - Montana -- General (Box 21)
  - Railroads (Box 21)
  - Red Lodge (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Rudyard (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Sidney (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Teton Range (Wyo. and Idaho) (Box 21)
  - Tournament of Roses (Box 21)
  - Whitefish (Mont.) (Box 21)
  - Yellowstone National Park (Box 21)
    - Fishing Bridge
    - Old Faithful Geyser
    - Viewbooks
    - Yellowstone Falls
    - Yellowstone Lake